Guide to the Campus Ministry Records 1954-1995
Pacific Lutheran University, Archives and Special Collections
- Student Congregation/University Congregation, 1955-1994; Series IV
  - Student Congregation Papers, 1955-1994; A
    - Treasurer's Log, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 12.16)
    - Treasurer's Log, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 12.17)
    - Student Congregation, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 12.18)
    - Student Congregation, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 13.1)
    - Student Congregation, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 13.2)
    - Student Congregation, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 13.3)
    - Student Congregation, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 13.4)
    - Student Congregation, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 13.5)
  - Student Congregation Bulletins, B
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 13.6)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 13.7)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 13.8)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 13.9)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 13.10)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 13.11)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 13.12)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 13.13)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 14.1)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 14.2)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 14.3)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 14.4)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 14.5)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 14.6)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 14.7)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 14.8)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 14.9)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 14.10)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 14.11)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 14.12)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 14.13)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 14.14)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 14.15)
    - Student Congregation Bulletins, 1989-2001 (Box-folder 14.16)